ABOUT

Frontend Engineer with a passion for making beautiful user-friendly interfaces based on research and data. Experienced in designing user interfaces with Sketch and Photoshop and conducting user research. Built multiple applications for managing internal business affairs and external customers.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

React, React Native, JavaScript, Typescript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, SASS, LESS, Gulp, Github, Git, Web Accessibility, Email coding

DESIGN

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, InVision, Sketch, Acrylic Painting, Illustrations, Photography

LANGUAGE

Japanese Language Proficiency Test (N1- Advanced) 2014 - Fluent in Japanese

Test of Chinese as a Foreign Language (Level 3) 2013 - Proficient in Mandarin

Conversant in Spanish

AWARDS

2017 (July) - Always Hungry Award

Awarded at Hungry for building the company's new website from the ground up and always working efficiently to produce excellent work.

2013 - Huayu Enrichment Scholarship

Awarded \$9,840 from the Taiwan Ministry of Education to study Mandarin in Taiwan











MAUREEN VOGEL

FRONTEND ENGINEER | UIUX LEAD

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND ENGINEER & UIUX LEAD

HUNGRY MARKETPLACE

Washington D.C. Metro Area July 2017 ~ Present

Hungry Marketplace is a startup that connects independent chefs to corporations that need catering.

- Build responsive, cross browser compatible applications from the ground up in JavaScript (React/React Native), Typescript, HTML & CSS.
- Create product prototypes using Sketch/Photoshop/InVision and conduct UI/UX research.
- Developed the frontend for Hungry's chef & catering menu selection platform & conducted user research to improve its checkout flow.
- Designed and built a website for Major League Baseball fans to order ballpark food to their homes during the Covid pandemic. It has generated over \$250,000 during the 2020 baseball season.
- Designed and built a React Native mobile app for users to find and view menus for Hungry catering popups near them.
- Built the frontend of the sales portal that is used by the internal sales team to manage all upcoming orders.
- Use Google Analytics to monitor website's performance and make adjustments accordingly.

FRONTEND ENGINEER

SYMPLICITY CORPORATION

Washington D.C. Metro Area July 2016 ~ July 2017

Symplicity offers a comprehensive suite of products for admissions, career services, advising, student conduct, campus life, housing & residence life, and alumni engagement offices.

- Maintained and updated software's user interface using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery, and tested for cross browser compatibility.
- Updated code to be ARIA/WCAG 2.0 compliant and used screen readers to test for web accessibility.
- Created new features from mocks provided by the UI/UX team including a dashboard with multiple charts using Javascript and Chart.js.

ART DIRECTOR

A2L CONSULTING

Washington D.C. Metro Area Apr. 2015 ~ Dec. 2015

A2L Consulting provides litigation consulting services and trial graphics.

- Advised lawyers on how to communicate their message through visual design to win in trial.
- Created persuasive graphics using Photoshop and PowerPoint to present to the judge and jury in court.
- Designed marketing, sales and promotional material using Photoshop & Illustrator.

EDUCATION